wordsofasahm.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy/Disclosure Policy - Words of a SAHM

This policy is valid from 01 May 2014  
This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact Jess at wordsofasahm dot com.  
This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.  
To get your own policy, go to [http://www.disclosurepolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)

## What information is collected from you?

I will collect your email address for the sole purpose of contacting you in case you win! If you subscribe to my emails via RSS or Mail Chimp, I will also have your emails for that. I don’t have registrations on my site, so when you visit, unless you comment, then I don’t get any information from you! When you comment on a blog post, your email is recorded there, but that’s not used for anything! 

## What is your information used for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  *  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

## How is your information protected?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## Are cookies used on this site?

Unless you want to provide me with some awesome peanut butter cookies fresh out of the oven or some fresh out of the oven chocolate chip cookies,  **We do not use cookies on this site!**

## **Is any information disclosed to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites

## **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

## **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on **5/1/2014**

## **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://wordsofasahm.com

Oak Grove, MO

US

jess@wordsofasahm.com
